[Music]
Hey.
What are you guys doing?
Getting ready to play cupcake slam.
Ooh, I wanna play.
Well, then hurry, grab a cupcake.
What's the bet?
Loser has to drink pickle juice.
Ew, I don't wanna drink pickle juice.
Well then, you better
throw that cupcake hard
and hope it's sticky.
That's not something
you hear every day.
Okay.
In five, four, three, two-- cupcakes.
You got this.
It's all you.
Oh my God.
You got everything.
Please go down.
You make me proud, boy.
You got it. It's all you.
It's all you.
You are-- oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, baby.
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, Sam.
You thirsty?
[Phone rings]
Oh.
That guy Jeffrey is on his way up.
Who's Jeffrey?
You know, the one who
e-mailed us about all the--
guess what just happened.
Your bellybutton started
talking to you.
No.
But that would be so cool.
"Galaxy wars."
I know.
Look at this.
A proton cruiser?
No, my proton cruiser.
I just bought it.
It was actually used in the
actual filming of "galaxy wars."
In the battle of Panthatar?
And the rescue of the horklops
from the planet Jooveron!
Shut up.
How can I?
Ziz-kwaja!
Wow.
I feel like I'm watching a
DVD of "dorks gone wild."
[Knocking]
Hi.
Hey, I'm Jeffrey Flanken.
Yeah, come on in.
Hi.
Hey.
This is Jeffrey, the guy whose
father owns Flanken motors.
Oh, right.
Your dad wants to set up some
kind of contest on iCarly?
Yeah.
I mean, if you guys are into it.
Look at my spaceship.
It's nice.
Well, let's go up to
our studio and talk.
Cool.
[Music]
In five, four, three, two-- [Music]
I know you see somehow
the world will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
I know somehow
were gonna get there
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm telling you
just how I feel
so, wake-up the members
of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance
unless you take one
take the time to see
the brighter side
of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give your best
[music]
Wait.
So, your dad wants to just
give away a brand-new car?
Yeah.
I mean, he does it
once every few years.
It's great publicity
for his dealership.
Cool.
So, what kind of contest?
How about guess the number
of zits on Freddie's butt?
Wow.
That's really gross.
No.
See, my dad wants the contest
to be a brain Buster.
You know, something you
really got to figure out.
Oh, like how many of Sam's
relatives are on parole?
Hey, don't go banging on my
aunt Maggie, cousin Garth,
and Uncle Morris, all right?
We're having a meeting.
So, we challenge our viewers to
figure out the brain Buster,
and then the first person who
sends in the right answer
wins the car?
Yup.
Love it.
It'll get iCarly a lot of buzz.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't your Uncle buzz on parole too?
Look Benson-- what, Sam?
He was a nice guy.
What are you going to do?
Stop it.
We'd love to do the
give-away-a-car contest.
Awesome.
All right.
Here's the brain Buster.
A cowboy rides into town on Friday.
He stays in town for three
days, then leaves on Friday.
How did he do it?
I have no idea.
I am not allowed to tell you.
See, to keep the contest
fair, my dad put the answer
in this sealed envelope.
Here, why don't you lock
this in your jewelry box.
My mom wanted a daughter, okay?
[Music]
And now, before we say goodnight--
it's time for an iCarly
special contest.
Special contest
special contest
okay.
Are you ready for this?
We are gonna give away
a new car-- a new car.
--From Flanken motors.
The best Flanken car
dealership in Seattle.
And to win the new car,
all you got to do
is answer this brain Buster.
Mood lighting.
Mysterious music.
[Music]
Okay.
Here's the brain Buster.
A cowboy rides into town on Friday.
He stays in town for three
days, then leaves on Friday.
How'd he do it?
Okay.
The first iCarly fan to
tell us the correct answer
wins a new car.
Just text us right here at iCarly.
Com.
And if you can't figure
out how to text us--
--then call your doctor.
--'Cause you may be suffering
from extreme stupidity.
Together, we can find a cure.
[Music]
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
[Makes beeping noises]
Uh-oh.
This is commander Spencer.
What is the nature of your emergency?
A fleet of red skynauts has
invaded the Alpha quadrant.
Seriously?
Seriously.
I will intercept and
destroy the enemy.
Oh God, thank you.
Shh.
[Hatch opening sound]
[Hatch closing sound]
Switching to hyperdrive.
[Makes hyperdrive sound]
Enemy ships within range.
Engaging.
Proton lasers set to maximosity.
I'm going in hot.
[Makes laser sounds]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I damage your ship?
Well, here.
Let me put it out of its misery.
[Makes laser sounds]
[Knock on door]
Hey, it's me.
Ah, teenage boy off the port bow.
[Makes laser sounds]
Whoa. You got it.
Yes.
[Hatch opening sound]
I did get it.
And now it's mine, and
the galaxy is safe.
[Makes laser sound]
Hey.
I thought you said this is one
of the actual proton cruisers
used to film "galaxy wars."
It is.
No, it's not.
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
And you're lying.
What makes you lie?
I'm not lying.
Yeah, you are.
Feel like a big boy telling
your big boy lies.
Spencer.
Yes, little Larry lies-a-lot?
The proton cruisers in "galaxy wars"
had twin exhaust ports up front.
This one only has one.
Well-- and the neutronium blast plate
is supposed to be octagonal.
That one's round.
But how can-- and look.
Here is a sticker that
says, "not an actual prop
from the movie 'galaxy wars.'"
okay.
Well, that can mean anything.
No.
It means this is just a replica.
But I paid for a real proton
cruiser from "galaxy wars."
Awwww!
Sorry, Spence.
I got to go rehearse iCarly.
[Music]
[Makes weak laser sound]
And then, the monster
rose up out of the coffin
and bit the man's head off.
[Screaming]
That was so scary.
How about a hand for George, the
bra who tells ghost stories.
Whoo. Yeah.
I hope you're ready
'cause the time has come.
The time has come.
If you have a hat, you
better hang on to it
'cause we're about to give
away a brand-new car.
Courtesy of Flanken motors.
You all know the brain Buster.
Which Carly will now repeat.
A cowboy rides into town on Friday.
He stays in town for three
days, then leaves on Friday.
How did he do it?
Let us check the envelope.
Oh.
I get it.
His horse's name was Friday.
Random dancing.
Okay.
A lot of you guys guessed
the right answer.
But only one of you guessed it first.
And that lucky winner's
screen name is trickster 206.
Wooo!
And now, Freddie will connect us
to the winner via video chat.
You just love saying via.
Yeah.
All right, we're connected.
Hey, trickster 206.
Guess what you've won?
Would it be a new car?
Nevel?
That's right, Carly Shay.
I've won the car, and you
have to give it to me.
Isn't this delicious?
Oh, I just feel like spinning
in a celebratory fashion.
Weeee! Weeee! Weeee!
Weeee! Weeee!
[music]
I wonder what kind of car
they're gonna give us.
You mean, give Nevel.
I can't believe that
nub won our contest.
Hey. Excuse me.
We're looking for the owner?
Well, stop looking.
Don Flanken.
What kind of car can I put you in?
We're from iCarly.
Yeah?
Well, I'm from Wisconsin.
So what kind of car
you're looking for?
Something sporty, something
functional, something spunctional--
look at me, I'm making up words.
That's how much I care about
putting you in the right car.
Now-- can you stop
talking for two seconds?
We're not here to buy a car.
We came to get-- hey, sir.
Dude, get back here.
Look, I don't have time for games.
We're not playing games.
We gave away one of your
cars on our Web show.
Well, who in blazes
told you to do that?
Your son.
He set up a contest.
I don't have a son,
just two daughters.
You don't have a son?
No--well, my oldest daughter
Jessica, she's a little manish
but I wouldn't say she's-- here he is.
Hello, iCarly people.
Where's my car?
We're getting it.
We may not be getting it.
What?
This nutloaf says he doesn't
know anything about our contest.
What?
Be quiet.
Make me.
All right.
I don't have time for this.
I gotta take my daughter
to a special doctor.
Wait.
Well.
iCarly ran an online contest.
I entered and I won a car.
And if you don't give me one,
I'm going to report you
to the LCC for fraud-- ooh.
--And have iCarly shut down.
Ooh.
[Music]
The.
Done.
All right.
Thanks a lot, guys.
And, here you go.
You're light.
Light?
You owe us 300.
Yeah.
But you said you'd move
my spaceship to storage
for a hundred bucks--100.
Plus 200 to bring the couch back.
Yeah.
Okay, wait.
A hundred to move out a huge
proton cruiser spaceship
and 200 just to bring back
this tiny little couch?
Hey, I had to miss my
book club for this.
We were gonna discuss the
sisters who had magic pants.
You owe us 200 more.
I don't have 200 more.
Hey, guys, you don't need
to take the couch away.
It's already here.
N.
I need that.
This is just creating more work.
That's my sittin' couch.
At the of the book, they find
out the pants aren't magic
and the middle sister dies.
[Faint laser sound]
And on your Web show, you
said all you gotta do
is answer this brain Buster,
and I was the first person
to send in the correct
answer to iCarly.com.
And then-- we know what happened!
We're not saying you
didn't win the car.
Then where is it?
I don't see a car.
All I hear is a lot prattle, and I-- hey.
Oh, come on.
Get it off me.
Oh, you'll get it.
Get up.
Come on.
Don't-- stop.
Now where is my car?
Do you not understand that there's
been some kind of mix up?
Well, let me read you this.
According to section 9 of the
Internet legislation act,
"any website "that engages
in fraud "will be subject
to immediate termination."
That means either you give me
a car or it's bye-bye iCarly.
If you'll just give us a couple
of days to get-- wait a minute.
Why do you have that printed out?
Because I like to print things.
No, you'd only print
that out if you knew
you were gonna need it.
Yeah.
How did you know there
was gonna be a problem
getting you the car?
Oh, please.
I don't have time to be interviewed.
You set this whole thing up.
That Jeffrey guy or
whatever his real name is,
you sent him to us, didn't you?
Oh, I don't know.
I send a lot of guys a lot of places.
You evil, evil little elf.
You can't prove anything, but I
can prove that you owe me a car
and I better get it or
you'll rue this day.
Rue it!
You'll get your car.
When?
Soon.
You have 48 hours, iCarly.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock,
tick-tock, tick-tock.
Hi.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm drinking root beer, playing Jacks.
Jacks?
I'm up to foursies-- threesies.
Where'd your proton cruiser go?
I paid some mean movers
to take it to storage.
How come?
'Cause it wasn't actually
used in galaxy wars,
so I don't wanna look at it.
Okay, so where's our couch?
You know, there's more to
life than couches, okay?
What?
I don't know.
How'd Nevel like his car?
There is no car.
What do you mean, no car?
Nevel set the whole thing up.
And if we don't get him a car,
he's gonna go to the LCC,
claim fraud, and get iCarly shut down.
Well, okay.
So get the little tug munch a car.
We can't afford to buy Nevel a car.
Maybe you can.
My buddy Socko's got an
uncle you sells used ones.
I bet he can find you a
car and super cheap.
Okay. What's his name?
Otto.
Of course, it is.
[Music]
Are you ready, Nevel?
Yes, my heart is pounding.
Good.
Maybe it'll explode.
I didn't come here to be insulted.
You don't even have a
car for me, do you?
Oh, yes, we do.
One-- two-- yank.
Whoa.
Oh, wow.
What is that poop?
It's your new car.
That car is not new.
It's new to you.
I suspected as much.
I figured you iCarlys would
try and pull a fast one.
Who still says "pull a fast one"?
Mr. bullock.
Over here, sir.
Look.
Look at the automotive abomination
that these people are trying
to foist upon me.
Well, I won't have it.
I simply won't.
Sir, our contest promised
the winner a car.
And that is a car.
Actually, I reviewed your Webcast.
You promised the winner a new
car and, well, this is poo.
Oh, comon.
Read them the rules.
The LCC defines a new car as,
"a unique vehicle that's
"never been state
registered "and can travel
"under it's own power "at the speed
of a least 25 miles per hour."
But come on.
Can't you give us a break?
I can give you another
24 hours, but by then,
if you don't give
Mr. Papperman a new car,
the LCC will shut down iCarly.
Sorry.
Thank you, Mr. bullock.
Winner says "ha-ha."
What's wrong with you, Nevel?
Why is your lifelong dream
to get rid of iCarly?
It's not.
My lifelong dream is to
open my own haberdashery.
What is a haberdashery?
Oh, why does everyone ask that?
A haberdashery is a men's retail shop
that sells men's accessories
such as wallets, hats, buttons,
belts, ribbons, and zippers.
[Music]
[Knocking]
What's up, Sam?
Where's Carly?
I've been calling and
texting her for hours.
Uh, she's been in the shower.
All day?
Pretty much.
She takes really long showers
when she gets depressed.
Well, when do you think
she'll come out?
I don't know.
She took a chair in there.
Carly, get out of the shower!
No.
Hey, you got your couch.
Yup.
I thought those mover guys wanted
200 bucks to bring it back.
They did, but Socko's cousin
only charged me 50 bucks
to steal it back.
Thanks, Rob.
So, you really think
Nevel's gonna have the LCC
shut down iCarly?
Yup, unless we can come
u with a unique vehicle
that's never been state
registered and can travel
under its own power at the speed
of at least 25 miles per hour.
By when tomorrow.
I know that look.
That's your thinking look.
Oh, I'm thinking.
You thinking?
Yeah, I'm thinking we
think of the same thing?
We are if we're thinking
about a way to give Nevel
a vehicle that's never
been state registered
and can go 25 miles an hour.
Oh, no.
I was thinking about fried chicken.
[Music]
These are good.
What is this? Pineapple?
Mango?
Maybe.
Well, it could be--
will you two shut up.
I'm about to rid the
Internet of iCarly forever
and you're bumming my joy.
Hey, Nevel, lookie.
[Music]
Here you go, Nevel.
Congratulations, winner.
What, and you think
that rolling space turd
will get iCarly off the hook?
Yeah.
We think it will.
Carly, would you say that
this vehicle is unique?
Oh, it is clearly unique.
Freddie, has it ever
been state registered?
Why, no, Carly.
It hasn't.
Mr. Bullock?
If it can travel at the speed
of at least 25 miles per hour,
it technically qualifies as a new car.
Well, let's just see.
Let's just see if
this thing can do 25.
Okay.
[Screams]
[Loud crash]
[Music]
Do you think he hit 25 miles an hour?
Oh, yeah.
You can't do that kind of
damage to a flower shop
unless you're doing at least 25.
[Sirens]
Where'd you guys get those ice-pops?
Over there.
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0